<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.kmag</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <developer id="org.kde">
    <name translate="no">KDE</name>
  </developer>
  <name>KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">العدسة</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="is">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="sa">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kmag</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">K Büyüteç</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="vi">KMag</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKMagxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">KMag 屏幕放大镜</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">KMag</name>
  <summary>Screen Magnifier</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">مكبَر الشاشة</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bg">Увеличител на екрана</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Lupa de la pantalla</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Lupa de la pantalla</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Lupa obrazovky</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Skærmforstørrer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Bildschirmlupe</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Μεγεθυντικός φακός οθόνης</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Screen Magnifier</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Ekranlupeo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Lupa de la pantalla</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Ekraani suurendusklaas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Pantailako lupa</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Suurennuslasi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Loupe d'écran</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Lupa da pantalla</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">זכוכית מגדלת למסך</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Képernyőnagyító</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Aggranditor de schermo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Memperbesar Layar</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="is">Skjástækkari</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Lente d'ingrandimento</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">ეკრანის გამადიდებელი</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">화면 돋보기</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lv">Ekrāna palielinātājs</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Schermvergroter</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Skjermforstørrar</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Lupa ekranowa</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Lupa do Ecrã</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Lupa da tela</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Lupă de ecran</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Экранная лупа</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sa">स्क्रीन आवर्धक</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Lupa obrazovky</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Povečevalnik zaslona</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Увеличавач екрана</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-Latn">Uveličavač ekrana</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Увеличавач екрана</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Uveličavač ekrana</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Skärmförstoringsglas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Ekran Büyüteci</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Збільшувач екрана</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="vi">Trình phóng đại màn hình</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxScreen Magnifierxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">屏幕放大镜</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">螢幕放大器</summary>
  <description>
    <p>KMag is a small utility for Linux to magnify a part of the screen. KMag is very useful for people with visual disabilities and for those working in the fields of image analysis, web development etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">تعد العدسة أداة مساعدة صغيرة لنظام لينكس لتكبير جزء من الشاشة. يعد برنامج العدسة مفيدًا جدًا للأشخاص ذوي الإعاقات البصرية ولأولئك الذين يعملون في مجالات تحليل الصور وتطوير الويب وما إلى ذلك.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">KMag е малка помощна програма за Linux за увеличаване на част от екрана. KMag е много полезна за хора със зрителни увреждания и за работещите в в областта на анализа на изображения, разработването на уеб сайтове и др.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KMag és una petita utilitat per al Linux per a ampliar una part de la pantalla. El KMag és molt útil per a persones amb discapacitats visuals i per a aquelles que treballen en els camps de l'anàlisi d'imatges, desenvolupament web, etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">KMag és una xicoteta utilitat per a Linux per a ampliar una part de la pantalla. KMag és molt útil per a persones amb discapacitats visuals i per a aquelles que treballen en els camps de l'anàlisi d'imatges, desenvolupament web, etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">KMag er et lille redskab til Linux som forstørrer en del af skærmen. KMag er meget nyttig til personer med synshandikap og dem der arbejder med billedanalyse, webudvikling osv.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">KMag ist ein kleines Dienstprogramm für Linux, um einen Teil des Bildschirms zu vergrößern. KMag ist sehr nützlich für Menschen mit Sehbehinderung und für Menschen, die in Bereichen der Bildanalyse, Webentwicklung usw. arbeiten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το KMag είναι μια μικρή εφαρμογή για Linux για να μεγεθύνει μέρος της οθόνης. Το KMag είναι πολύ χρήσιμο για ανθρώπους με δυσκολίες στην όραση και για εκείνους που ασχολούνται με τα πεδία της ανάλυσης εικόνας, ανάπτυξης εφαρμογών ιστού κλπ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KMag is a small utility for Linux to magnify a part of the screen. KMag is very useful for people with visual disabilities and for those working in the fields of image analysis, web development etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">KMag estas malgranda ilo por Linukso por pligrandigi parton de la ekrano. KMag estas tre utila por homoj kun vidaj handikapoj kaj por tiuj laborantaj en la kampoj de bildanalizo, TTT-evoluigo ktp.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KMag es una pequeña utilidad para Linux que aumenta una parte de la pantalla. KMag resulta muy útil para personas con problemas visuales y para los que trabajan en campos de análisis de imágenes, desarrollo web, etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">KMag on Linuxi väike abivahend ekraani osade suurendamiseks. KMag on suureks abiks nägemispuudega inimestele, samuti neile, kelle erialaks on pildianalüüs, veebiarendus jne.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">KMag pantailaren zati bat handitzeko Linux-erako baliagarritasun txiki bat da. KMag oso baliagarria da ikusmenean ezintasuna dutenentzako, baita irudi analisian, web diseinuan eta beste hainbat eremutan lan egiten dutenentzako ere.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">KMag on pieni Linux-työkalu näytön osan suurentamiseksi. KMagista on hyötyä heikkonäköisille, kuvia tarkoin tutkiville tai esimerkiksi verkkokehitystä tekeville.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KMag est un petit utilitaire Linux qui permet de zoomer sur une partie de l'écran. KMag est très utile pour les personnes atteintes de déficiences visuelles ou travaillant dans les domaines de l'analyse d'images, du développement Web, etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">KMag é unha pequena utilidade para Linux para aumentar unha parte da pantalla. KMag é moi útil para a xente con discapacidades visuais e para traballadores dos campos de análise de imaxes, desenvolvemento web, etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">KMag הוא כלי קטן ללינוקס להגדלת חלק מהמסך. KMag הוא מאוד שימוש לאנשים עם מוגבלות ראייה ולאלו שעובדים כתחומי ניתוח תמונות, פיתוח אתרים ועוד.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A KMag egy kis segédprogram Linuxhoz a képernyő egy részének nagyítására. A KMag nagyon hasznos a látássérültek és a képelemzés, webfejlesztés, és egyéb területen dolgozók számára.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">KMag es un parve utilitate per Linux per aggrandir un parte de schermo. KMag es multe utile per gente con dishabilitates visual e illos travaliante in le campos del analysis de image, disveloppamento web etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">KMag adalah utilitas kecil buat Linux untuk memperbesar bagian layar. KMag sangat berguna bagi para penyandang cacat visual dan bagi mereka yang bekerja di bidang analisis gambar, pengembangan web, dll.</p>
    <p xml:lang="is">KMag er lítið nytjatól fyrir Linux til að stækka hluta af skjánum. KMag nýtist vel fólki sem á við einhverskonar sjónskerðingu að stríða, en ekki síður þeim sem vinna við myndgreiningar eða vefhönnun, svo eitthvað sé talið.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KMag è un piccolo programma per ingrandire una parte dello schermo. È molto utile alle persone con disabilità visive e per quelli che lavorano nel campo dell'analisi delle immagini, dello sviluppo web ecc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">KMag პატარა პროგრამაა Linux-სთვის, ეკრანის ნაწილის გასადიდებლად. ის გამოადგებათ ხალხს, რომელსაც მხედველობის პრობლემა აქვთ და მათ, ვინც გამოსახულებების ანალიზზე, ვებ-დეველოპმენტზე და ა.შ. მუშაობენ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">KMag은 리눅스용 화면 돋보기입니다. 시각 장애가 있는 사용자나 이미지 분석, 웹 개발 등에 유용합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">„KMag“ ir maza „Linux“ utilītprogramma ekrāna daļas palielināšanai. „KMag“ ir ļoti noderīgs rīks cilvēkiem ar redzes traucējumiem vai cilvēkiem, kuri strādā ar attēlu analīzi, tīmekļa izstrādi u.tml.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KMag is een klein hulpprogramma voor Linux om een deel van het scherm te vergroten. KMag is erg nuttig voor mensen met een visuele beperking en voor hen die werken in het veld van analyse van afbeeldingen, webontwikkeling etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">KMag er eit lite verktøy for å forstørra delar av skjermen. Det er veldig nyttig for alle med nedsett syn og for dei som arbeider med for eksempel biletanalyse eller utvikling av nettsider.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KMag jest małym narzędziem dla Linuksa do powiększania części ekranu. KMag jest bardzo użytecznym programem dla osób z niepełnosprawnością wzroku, a także dla tych, którzy pracują przy analizie obrazów i tworzeniu stron internetowych, itp.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KMag é um pequeno utilitário para o Linux aumentar uma parte do ecrã. O KMag é muito útil para as pessoas com incapacidades visuais e para aqueles que trabalham na área de análise de imagens, desenvolvimento na Web, etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O KMag é um pequeno utilitário para Linux para ampliar uma parte da tela. O  KMag é muito útil para pessoas com deficiências visuais e para aqueles trabalhando em campos de análise de imagens, desenvolvimento Web, etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">KMag — это небольшое приложение для Linux, позволяющее увеличивать часть экрана. Приложение KMag очень полезно для людей с нарушениями зрения и тех, кто работает в области анализа изображений, веб-разработки и схожих областях.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sa">KMag इति Linux कृते स्क्रीनस्य भागं वर्धयितुं लघुः उपयोगिता अस्ति । दृष्टिविकलाङ्गजनानाम् अपि च प्रतिबिम्बविश्लेषणं, जालविकासादिक्षेत्रेषु कार्यं कुर्वतां कृते KMag अतीव उपयोगी अस्ति ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KMag je malý nástroj pre Linux na zväčšenie časti obrazovky. KMag je veľmi užitočný pre ľudí so zrakovým postihnutím a pre tých čo pracujú v oblasti analýzy obrazu, vývoja webových aplikácií atď.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">KMag je majhen pripomoček za Linux za povečanje dela zaslona. KMag je zelo koristen za osebe z motnjami vida in za tiste, ki delajo na področjih analize slik, spletnega razvoja itd.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kmag är ett litet verktyg för Linux som förstorar en del av skärmen. Kmag är mycket användbart för personer med synfel och för de som arbetar inom fälten bildanalys, webbutveckling, etc.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">K Büyüteç, Linux için yapılmış ekranınızın bir köşesini büyütmeye yarayan ufak bir izlencedir. KMag, görsel zorlukları olan kişiler ve görsel çözümlemesi veya web geliştirmesi gibi alanlarda çalışan kişiler için pek yararlıdır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KMag — невеличка програма для Linux, призначенням якої є збільшення зображення частини екрана. KMag є дуже корисною програмою для людей із вадами зору та тих, хто працює у галузях аналізу зображень, веброзробки тощо.</p>
    <p xml:lang="vi">KMag là một tiện ích nhỏ cho Linux để phóng đại một phần của màn hình. KMag rất hữu ích cho người có khuyết tật thị giác và người làm việc trong các ngành như phân tích ảnh, phát triển web, v.v.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKMag is a small utility for Linux to magnify a part of the screen. KMag is very useful for people with visual disabilities and for those working in the fields of image analysis, web development etc.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">KMag 是一款为 Linux 设计的用于放大显示一定屏幕区域的小工具。KMag 可以帮助视力障碍用户看清屏幕内容，也可以在图像分析或者网页开发等领域发挥辅助作用。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">KMag 是個給 Linux 用來放大螢幕區塊的小工具。KMag 是個對有視覺障礙、從事圖片分析或網頁開發…的使用者十分有用的工具。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://apps.kde.org/kmag</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kmag</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kmag</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=kmag&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>KMag in action</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">العدسة وهي تعمل</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">KMag в действие</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">El KMag en acció</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">KMag en acció</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">KMag i brug</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">KMag in Aktion</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Το KMag σε δράση</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">KMag in action</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">KMag en aktivo</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">KMag en acción</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">KMag tegevuses</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">KMag martxan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">KMag toiminnassa</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">KMag en action</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">KMag en acción</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">KMag בפעולה</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">A KMag akcióban</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">KMag in action</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">KMag beraksi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="is">KMag að verki</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">KMag in azione</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">KMag -ის გამოყენება</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">KMag 사용 모습</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">„KMag“ darbībā</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">KMag in actie</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">KMag i praksis</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">KMag w działaniu</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">O KMag em acção</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">KMag em ação</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">KMag în acțiune</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">KMag в действии</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sa">केमाग् कर्मणि</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">KMag v akcií</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">KMag v akciji</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Kmag i aktion</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">K Büyüteç çalışırken</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">KMag у дії</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="vi">Sử dụng KMag</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxKMag in actionxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">KMag 的工作状态</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">KMag 正使用中</caption>
      <image type="source" width="1090" height="841">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kmag/kmag.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kmag</binary>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.kmag.desktop</launchable>
  <releases>
    <release version="25.08.0" date="2025-08-14"/>
    <release version="25.04.3" date="2025-07-03"/>
    <release version="25.04.2" date="2025-06-05"/>
    <release version="25.04.1" date="2025-05-08"/>
    <release version="25.04.0" date="2025-04-17"/>
    <release version="24.12.3" date="2025-03-06"/>
    <release version="24.12.2" date="2025-02-06"/>
    <release version="24.12.1" date="2025-01-09"/>
    <release version="24.12.0" date="2024-12-12"/>
    <release version="24.08.3" date="2024-11-07"/>
    <release version="24.08.2" date="2024-10-10"/>
    <release version="24.08.1" date="2024-09-12"/>
    <release version="24.08.0" date="2024-08-22"/>
    <release version="24.05.2" date="2024-07-04"/>
    <release version="24.05.1" date="2024-06-13"/>
    <release version="24.05.0" date="2024-05-23"/>
    <release version="24.02.2" date="2024-04-11"/>
    <release version="24.02.1" date="2024-03-21"/>
    <release version="24.02.0" date="2024-02-28"/>
    <release version="23.08.5" date="2024-02-15"/>
  </releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
</component>
